8/15 6482 st. Yali mh / Karsiyaka.

Izmir, 35550

+90 (530) 485 2635

+61 401 773 422

https://volgak.vercel.app https://www.behance.net/volgailgiz volgailgiz92@gmail.com

VOLGA ILGIZ KARADAGOGLU

Visual Designer & Illustrator

SUMMARY

I am an illustrator and visual designer with a passion for creating immersive and interactive experiences. I am a quick learner and have a strong ability to pick up new technologies quickly.

I have 5+ years of both corporate and freelance experience in handling graphic design, animation, illustration. I am a creative and innovative thinker, with a strong ability to bring concepts to life. My time as a freelance designer has taught me how to make clients happy.

EXPERIENCE

Wallace Building Systems, Melbourne — Graphic Artist (full-time)

OCTOBER 2023 - SEPTEMBER 2024

- Design visuals for both printed and digital media.
- Create marketing collateral.
- Update visual branding of sub-brands, Gateway, Biolink and Wild Things.
- Create appealing social media posts.
- Design packaging for various products.
- Create motion graphics for various uses such as COVID test instructions and menu board display.

Teos Animation Studios, Izmir — Character Artist (contract)

SEPTEMBER 2023 - FEBRUARY 2024

- Created assets for an interactive motion book.
- Designed characters in designated style. Placed them into the software ready for rigging

Palto Tasarim, Eskisehir — Lead Visual Designer (full-time)

FEBRUARY 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2022

- Designed the visuals for printing on products.
- Designed website visuals.
- Created appealing social media posts.
- Controlled speed and quality of production process.
- Designed one of the most sold products on no: 1 eCommerce site of the country.

Centrum Time, Istanbul — Layout Designer (contract)

FEBRUARY 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2017

• Designed layout and cover of the magazine suitable for digital and printed media.

Artnefer Design Office, Eskisehir — Jr. Art Director (full-time)

July 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2017

- Coordinated with clients to create eye catching social media graphics
- Illustrated assets for infographic for nation-wide companies
- Developed consistent branding with detailed guidelines
- Designed menus, fliers, brochures, posters and other printed media

EDUCATION

Anadolu University, Eskisehir — Bachelor of Arts

SEPTEMBER 2011 - FEBRUARY 2019

AWARDS & EVENTS

Indo NFT Festiverse, Art Pop - Up

04/2022 - Yogyakarta, Indonesia.

TOOLBOX

Adobe Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects and Indesign,

Animation & 3D: Moho Pro, Toon Boom, Rive, Spline, Beginner on Blender

Coding: Beginner on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Swift

SOFT SKILLS

Innovative thinking, Hunger for learning more, Problem solver, Quick learner, Team member